♪ (PLAYING UPBEAT SONG
ON KEYBOARD) ♪
♪ If I didn't have you
♪ Life would be blue
♪ I'd be Doctor Who
without the TARDIS
(Sheldon:)Is it me,
or does she not look so good?
♪ A candle without a wick
A Watson without a Crick
♪ I'd be one of my outfits
without a dickey
♪ I'd be cheese without the mac
♪ Jobs without the Wozniak
♪ I'd be solving
exponential equations
♪ That use bases
not found on your calculator
♪ Making it much harder to crack
♪ I'd be an atom without a bomb
♪ A dot without the com
♪ And I'd probably still live
with my mom
♪ And he'd probably still live
with his mom
♪ Ever since I met you,
you turned my world around
♪ You supported all my dreams
and all my hopes
♪ You're like uranium-235
and I'm uranium-238
♪ Almost inseparable isotopes